

www.trangerthings.com www.behance.net/trangtt42714e5 trangtt427@gmail.com (925) 352-3373



# PROFILE

A creative thinker with 7+ years of combined UX design, visual design and print experience. I like to approach design issues with the capacity of a user, thinking about the best ways to communicate a business goal in the simplest form.



#### EXPERIENCE

# **Engagio - Designer**

January 2018 - present

- Conceptualize original website design ideas that bring simplicity and friendliness to user experience
- Help establish and promote design guidelines, best practices and standards
- Create wireframes, storyboards, user flows, process flows and web pages to communicate interaction and design ideas
- Design print material for marketing collateral and graphics for ads
- Own the design and flow of website

## Controlco - UX Designer/Front End Developer

September 2016 - October 2017

- Collaborated with building automations team to create IoT applications, both mobile and desktop, for clients to control facility operational settings
- Designed and developed dashboards, alarm consoles, and other entities to track building innerworkings using HTML/CSS, some javascript, Niagara 4 and DGLux5
- Designed interfaces that allowed clients to interact with cloud data from installed equipment
- Provided wireframes, user storyboards, mock-ups, and prototypes using tools like Sketch, InVision, Photoshop, and Illustrator

## Freelance - UX/Visual Designer

August 2008 - Current

- Design both digital and print collateral using Illustrator, Photoshop, and InDesign
- Ideate and provide artistic critique of client ideas
- Help clients define brand guidelines and standards
- Establish intuitive user flows and interactions for websites and apps



#### EDUCATION

University of California, San Diego Extension 2018 - 2019 User Experience (UX) Design Certificate Program

University of California, Santa Barbara 2012 - 2014 B.S. Biology, emphasis in psychobiology



#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

### Skills

User research

Lo-fi & hi-fi mock-ups

Wireframing & storyboarding

Iterative design

Prototyping

HTML/CSS

Print design

Visual design

Color theory

Typography

Iconography

### Software

Sketch

InVision

Photoshop

Illustrator

InDesign

AutoCAD

Final Cut

SketchUp

Maya